I killed her. She has come back to kill me.
لقد قتلتها، وعادت لتقتلني.
Do you believe Mia's mother is still alive?
هل تعتقد أن والدة ميا لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
That it's possible, she could return?
هل من الممكن أن تعود؟
I'm open to the possibility. You'll need to protect her.
أنا منفتح على هذا الاحتمال. عليك حمايتها.
- Can you stay at Jason's? - Why?
- هل يمكنك البقاء عند جيسون؟ - لماذا؟
I've got something to take care of in Montanesa.
لدي شيء لأعتني به في مونتانيسا.
Patpat doesn't like anyone. Only Matmat.
باتبات لا يحب أي شخص. مطمات فقط.
I'll make Patrick happy.
سأجعل باتريك سعيدًا.
The kind of happiness he'll never forget.
هذا النوع من السعادة لن ينساه أبدًا.
- Three! - Ahh!
- ثلاثة! - آه!
Yeah!
نعم!
Whoo!
وو!
Yeah, that's it, Matmat. Patrick said you should be here for now.
أجل، هذا كل شيء يا ماتمات. قال باتريك إنه يجب أن تكون هنا الآن.
You'll be alone in that mansion.
ستكون وحيدًا في هذا القصر.
M-My session with Doc is canceled?
م- تم إلغاء جلستي مع الطبيب؟
Yes, Matmat. That's why you should stay here for now.
نعم يا مطمت. لهذا السبب عليك البقاء هنا الآن.
- Okay? Let's go. But…
حسنًا؟ لنذهب. لكن...
But Matmat doesn't like your room.
ولكن ماتمات لا يحب غرفتك.
I'd rather stay in my and Patpat's room.
أفضل البقاء في غرفتي مع باتبات.
Oh, oh! Fine. I'll come with you.
أوه، أوه! حسنًا. سآتي معك.
You're not allowed--What the--
لا يُسمح لك--ماذا--
I think a Tikbalang is getting married.
أعتقد أن تيكبالانج سيتزوج.
What's this? What's happening here?
ما هذا؟ ماذا يحدث هنا؟
- What's this?! A nice little break.
- ما هذا؟! استراحة قصيرة لطيفة.
I'm on vacation, right?
أنا في إجازة، أليس كذلك؟
To cool down.
للتبريد.
What's with the wind? All people think about is a vacation.
ما بال الريح؟ كل ما يفكر فيه الناس هو العطلة.
Hi, Sir Vincent!
مرحبًا، السيد فينسنت!
Hi, Matmat!
مرحبًا، ماتمات!
My newest illustrator.
رسامي الأحدث.
You know what, not that you're asking--
هل تعلم ماذا، ليس أنك تسأل--
- No one's asking. Usually,
لا أحد يسأل. عادةً ،
I'm in El Nido, Maldives…
أنا في إل نيدو، جزر المالديف…
Ah, go book a flight then. Go! Don't come back--
آه، احجز رحلة إذن. انطلق! لا تعُد--
No! Shhh!
لا! ششش!
You see this? I need to compromise for now.
هل ترى هذا؟ عليّ أن أتنازل الآن.
The company is suffering a setback. It's not earning much.
الشركة تعاني من نكسة. أرباحها قليلة.
But, Matmat!
ولكن، ماتمات!
If you do your best and work well with Mia,
إذا بذلت قصارى جهدك وعملت بشكل جيد مع ميا،
we'll earn a lot. That's why, you should finish the book quickly.
سنربح الكثير. لذا، عليك إنهاء الكتاب بسرعة.
So we can get back the losses. Okay? Please!
حتى نتمكن من تعويض خسائرنا. حسنًا؟ من فضلك!
You know what Vincent, I don't understand…
أنت تعرف ماذا يا فينسنت، أنا لا أفهم...
how you put the effort to fill this up and inflate the pool
كيف بذلت الجهد لملء هذا المسبح ونفخه؟
when the ocean is right there!
عندما يكون المحيط هناك!
Aren't you getting goosebumps from--
ألا تشعر بالقشعريرة من--
Aren't you ashamed that Gemma might see you like this?
ألا تشعر بالخجل من أن جيما قد تراك بهذا الشكل؟
Jason,
جيسون،
- I think that's the point.
- أعتقد أن هذه هي النقطة.
- Gemma shouldn't see this
- لا ينبغي لجيما أن ترى هذا
because Sir Vincent is taking a bath.
لأن السير فينسنت يأخذ حمامًا.
You're right, Matmat. Let's go.
أنت محق يا مطمت. هيا بنا.
- Sir Vincent. - Hmm?
- السير فينسنت. - همم؟
Cover yourself. So cocky!
غطِّ نفسك. يا لك من مغرور!
Come on, Matmat.
هيا يا مطمت.
I love it here.
انا احبه هنا.
That was so much fun.
لقد كان ممتعا للغاية.
You didn't seem scared earlier.
لم يبدو عليك الخوف في وقت سابق.
I wasn't scared at all.
لم أكن خائفة على الإطلاق.
I love that this was spontaneous.
أحب أن هذا كان عفويًا.
'Cause I get to see the fun side of you.
لأنني أرى الجانب الممتع منك.
- Now, let's take a picture. - Mia.
- الآن دعونا نلتقط صورة. - ميا.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's take pictures so you have memories to keep.
دعونا نلتقط الصور حتى يكون لديك ذكريات يمكنك الاحتفاظ بها.
There.
هناك.
Ready?
مستعد؟
Smile.
يبتسم.
Can't you do a bigger smile?
ألا يمكنك أن تبتسم بشكل أكبر؟
Come on. Smile!
هيا، ابتسم!
Smile like you mean it.
ابتسم وكأنك تعني ذلك.
One, two, three!
واحد اثنين ثلاثة!
Yes!
نعم!
One more. One, two, three!
واحد آخر. واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة!
Let's take a picture together.
دعونا نلتقط صورة معًا.
There.
هناك.
Closer.
أقرب.
There you go.
هناك تذهب.
One, two, three!
واحد اثنين ثلاثة!
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
You know what, you're cute when you're smiling.
هل تعلم ماذا، أنت لطيف عندما تبتسم.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
No, let's find another angle. This one's good.
لا، لنبحث عن زاوية أخرى. هذه جيدة.
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
I have to get this. It might be an emergency.
عليّ الحصول على هذا. قد يكون أمرًا طارئًا.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Your eyes…
عيناك…
I feel like I've seen them before.
أشعر وكأنني رأيتهم من قبل.
Do you remember me now?
هل تتذكرني الآن؟
Samuel?
صموئيل؟
It's you.
إنه أنت.
I've missed you.
لقد افتقدتك.
I've missed you, Samuel.
لقد افتقدتك يا صموئيل.
You died already!
لقد مت بالفعل!
You died!
لقد مت!
- Samuel! - You're supposed to be dead!
- صموئيل! - من المفترض أن تكون ميتًا!
It's me!
هذا أنا!
You're not supposed to be alive! You died!
لا ينبغي لك أن تكون حيًا! لقد مت!
- Go. Do it, Samuel. - Die! Die!
- انطلق. افعلها يا صموئيل. - مت! مت!
That's what happens to people who meddle.
هذا ما يحدث للأشخاص الذين يتدخلون.
Sorry.
آسف.
- Sorry… - I understand why you did that.
- آسف... - أفهم لماذا فعلت ذلك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
At least, Samuel,
على الأقل، صموئيل،
you remember me now.
لقد تذكرتني الآن.
Sorry, sorry.
عذرا، عذرا.
Samuel…
صموئيل…
- Where are they? - They're over there, sir.
- أين هم؟ - إنهم هناك، سيدي.
- Over that deck. Okay. - Thank you, ma'am.
- فوق السطح. حسنًا. - شكرًا لكِ سيدتي.
Who's there? It's Miss Mia!
من هناك؟ إنها الآنسة ميا!
Why did you sneak out?
لماذا تسللت للخارج؟
Patrick.
باتريك.
You know I didn't get the chance to say goodbye to Bella, right?
هل تعلم أنني لم أحصل على فرصة قول وداعًا لبيللا، أليس كذلك؟
How did you escape?
كيف هربت؟
Come on, hurry.
هيا، اسرع.
Dr. Anok never locks his van. You can sneak out with this.
الدكتور أنوك لا يقفل شاحنته أبدًا. يمكنك التسلل بها.
See? Get in.
هل رأيت؟ ادخل.
Hurry, get inside.
اسرع، ادخل إلى الداخل.
Here, take this.
هنا، خذ هذا.
I got all the nurses' numbers from reception and listed them there.
حصلت على أرقام جميع الممرضات من الاستقبال وقمت بإدراجها هناك.
If anything goes wrong, just call them.
إذا حدث أي خطأ، فقط اتصل بهم.
Miss Cynthia and Mister Tommy,
السيدة سينثيا والسيد تومي،
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I promise I'll make it up to you.
أعدك بأنني سأعوضك.
Just go ahead and hide.
فقط اذهب واختبئ.
Doc didn't notice you were hiding in the back?
هل لاحظ الطبيب أنك كنت مختبئًا في الخلف؟
He didn't see me.
لم يراني.
When he pulled over at a bakery, I made my move and slipped out.
عندما توقف عند المخبز، تحركت وتسللت للخارج.
I just really want to be with Kai, just for today.
أريد حقًا أن أكون مع كاي، فقط لهذا اليوم.
You know that my dad's going to take me to New York?
هل تعلم أن والدي سيأخذني إلى نيويورك؟
I don't know
لا أعرف
when we'll see each other again.
عندما نرى بعضنا البعض مرة أخرى.
Patrick,
باتريك،
I promise to go back to the hospital tomorrow.
أعدك أن أعود إلى المستشفى غدًا.
Also, can I borrow some money to pay for our room?
هل يمكنني أيضًا اقتراض بعض المال لدفع تكاليف غرفتنا؟
I won't tell anyone you helped me.
لن أخبر أحداً أنك ساعدتني.
No.
لا.
You're going home and we're going back to the hospital. Come on.
أنت ذاهب إلى المنزل ونحن ذاهبون إلى المستشفى. هيا.
Hey, Patrick, wait!
مهلا، باتريك، انتظر!
Please, take pity on us.
من فضلك ارحمنا.
To be honest, this is your fault.
بصراحة، هذا خطؤك.
How's it my fault?
كيف يكون خطئي؟
Patrick, if you didn't hit my ex, then,
باتريك، إذا لم تضرب حبيبي السابق، إذن،
then there wouldn't be any trouble.
حينها لن تكون هناك أي مشكلة.
Papa wouldn't have dragged me out of the hospital.
لن يخرجني أبي من المستشفى.
Uh, bro…
أوه، أخي...
When you punched Bella's ex,
عندما لكمت حبيب بيلا السابق،
I said to myself,
قلت لنفسي
if Patrick who always watches his temper
إذا كان باتريك يراقب مزاجه دائمًا
couldn't hold it anymore,
لم أستطع التحمل أكثر من ذلك،
maybe I should also not hold back my feelings for Bella.
ربما لا ينبغي لي أيضًا أن أكتم مشاعري تجاه بيلا.
It's true.
إنه صحيح.
They're right.
إنهم على حق.
You are to blame for all of this.
أنت المسؤول عن كل هذا.
That's why
لهذا السبب
I already paid for your rooms.
لقد دفعت بالفعل ثمن غرفتك.
And also our room.
وغرفتنا أيضا.
Really, Miss Mia?
حقا يا آنسة ميا؟
Thank you, Miss Mia! Thank you! Thank you so much!
شكراً لكِ يا آنسة ميا! شكراً جزيلاً!
- You're welcome. - You're the best!
- مرحباً بك. - أنت الأفضل!
I can't stay here overnight.
لا أستطيع البقاء هنا طوال الليل.
You're going to leave them?
هل ستتركهم؟
If we go, you're going to leave your patients.
إذا ذهبنا، فسوف تترك مرضاك.
Technically, I'm suspended. Why should I look after them?
تقنيًا، أنا مُعلّق. لماذا عليّ أن أعتني بهم؟
If you're suspended,
إذا تم إيقافك،
why are you insisting on getting Kai back to the hospital?
لماذا تصر على إعادة كاي إلى المستشفى؟
Yeah, bro. Miss Mia is right.
نعم يا أخي، الآنسة ميا على حق.
Come on, Patrick.
تعال يا باتريك.
You were the one who inspired them to do all this.
لقد كنت أنت الذي ألهمهم للقيام بكل هذا.
Let's stay here for the night.
دعونا نبقى هنا طوال الليل.
Then first thing tomorrow, we'll get Kai back to the hospital.
ثم أول شيء غدًا، سنعيد كاي إلى المستشفى.
- Dear! - Hello, Ma!
- عزيزي! - مرحباً يا أمي!
Come on.
تعال.
- Have a seat. - Hello, Matmat.
- اجلس. - مرحبا مطمات.
Where's Patrick?
أين باتريك؟
Uh, he's not here. He has to go to Montanesa.
هو ليس هنا. عليه أن يذهب إلى مونتانيسا.
That's why Matmat is staying here.
ولهذا السبب يبقى مطمت هنا.
H-He…
هـ-هـ…
Patpat has to go somewhere.
باتبات يجب أن يذهب إلى مكان ما.
He'll be home late.
سوف يعود إلى المنزل متأخرًا.
Ah!
اه!
Matmat, how's your job working with Mia?
مطمت، كيف هو عملك مع ميا؟
Have you done a lot?
هل فعلت الكثير؟
W-We haven't done any.
و- لم نفعل أي شيء.
Because she hasn't had any ideas yet.
لأنها لم تكن لديها أية أفكار بعد.
But I gained a best friend.
ولكنني حصلت على صديق أفضل.
Really? You're best friends now?
حقاً؟ هل أصبحتما أفضل صديقين الآن؟
I-It's Mia.
أنا ميا.
She said we're best friends. She's my bestie now.
قالت إننا أفضل صديقتين. وهي الآن صديقتي المفضلة.
If you guys are best friends, you should invite her here.
إذا كنتم أفضل الأصدقاء، يجب أن تدعوها هنا.
She's not here.
إنها ليست هنا.
Uh, What do you mean? Where's Mia?
أوه، ماذا تقصد؟ أين ميا؟
I-I don't know. She also went out.
لا أعلم، لقد خرجت أيضًا.
Huh? Both of them are gone?
هاه؟ كلاهما رحلوا؟
Maybe Patrick and Miss Mia are together?
ربما باتريك والسيدة ميا معًا؟
Oh, please, Madeth.
أوه، من فضلك، ماديث.
Are you a writer too like Mia? You're making such plot twists.
هل أنتِ كاتبة مثل ميا؟ تُحدثين تحولات في الأحداث.
No. Just maybe, right?
لا، ربما فقط، أليس كذلك؟
Patrick went out and Miss Mia too.
خرج باتريك والآنسة ميا أيضًا.
And wherever Patrick is, Miss Mia's there too.
وأينما كان باتريك، فإن الآنسة ميا موجودة هناك أيضًا.
- Who knows they might be-- - Say 'ahh'.
- من يدري فقد يكونون-- - قل "آه".
Ah! Very good. There.
آه! جيد جدًا. هناك.
- Oh, Madeth. - Just maybe.
- أوه، ماديث. - ربما فقط.
Just maybe.
ربما فقط.
Let's not speak about the ones who aren't here. Eat up, eat up.
دعونا لا نتحدث عن الغائبين. كُلوا، كُلوا.
Here. Eat up.
هنا. تناول الطعام.
- Dear, please eat. - Yeah. Matmat, here.
- عزيزي، تفضل بالأكل. - نعم. مطمت، هنا.
Do you want this?
هل تريد هذا؟
Patrick?
باتريك؟
Patrick, look.
باتريك، انظر.
The owner gave it to us.
لقد أعطاها لنا المالك.
It's flavored coconut liquor.
إنه مشروب جوز الهند بنكهة.
Do you think it's safe to drink?
هل تعتقد أنه من الآمن شربه؟
Maybe it's a local product.
ربما يكون منتج محلي.
If I die from drinking this,
إذا مت من شرب هذا،
tell the funeral parlor to do my makeup well
أخبر دار الجنازة أن يقوموا بمكياجي جيدًا
or else my spirit won't be at peace.
وإلا فلن تنعم روحي بالسلام.
I just need to call someone.
أريد فقط أن أتصل بشخص ما.
Okay. Then let's drink?
حسناً. إذن دعنا نشرب؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hello, Matmat…
مرحباً، مطمت…
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Matmat is just drawing before going to sleep.
ماتمات يرسم فقط قبل الذهاب إلى النوم.
Are you on your way home, Patpat?
هل أنت في طريقك إلى المنزل، باتبات؟
The thing is, uh…
الحقيقة هي، اه...
I might be home in the morning.
ربما أكون في المنزل في الصباح.
Why? Are there no more buses?
لماذا؟ هل لا يوجد المزيد من الحافلات؟
No, it's uh…
لا، إنه...
I need to accompany someone.
أريد أن أرافق شخصًا ما.
Uh, a patient.
أوه ، مريض.
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
Are you at M-Mama Li's?
هل أنت في M-Mama Li's؟
No, but I'm okay, Matmat.
لا، ولكنني بخير، مطمت.
O-Okay.
حسنًا.
Wake up early tomorrow so you can commute faster.
استيقظ مبكرًا غدًا حتى تتمكن من التنقل بشكل أسرع.
Okay, Matmat.
حسنًا، مطمت.
Don't forget to brush your teeth and your hair before bed. Okay?
لا تنسَ تنظيف أسنانك وشعرك قبل النوم. حسنًا؟
Matmat knows that. I can take care of myself.
مطمت يعرف ذلك. أنا قادر على الاعتناء بنفسي.
Okay. Call me if you need me.
حسنًا، اتصل بي إذا احتجتني.
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay. You too.
حسنًا. وأنت أيضًا.
Good night, Matmat.
تصبح على خير مطمت.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
So this is what it's like to be someone's secret lover.
لذا، هذا هو ما يشبه أن تكون عشيقًا سريًا لشخص ما.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
I feel like a mistress you're hiding from the legal wife
أشعر وكأنني عشيقة تخفيها عن الزوجة الشرعية
because you haven't told Matmat that you're here with me.
لأنك لم تخبر ماتمات بأنك هنا معي.
When have the mistress and the wife ever been besties?
متى كانت العشيقة والزوجة أفضل صديقتين؟
But thank you.
ولكن شكرا لك.
For being your secret lover?
لأني حبيبك السري؟
For being Matmat's friend.
لأنه صديق مطماطة.
That was Mama's dream for him.
كان هذا حلم ماما له.
You made it come true
لقد جعلته حقيقة
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
I think this calls for a celebration.
أعتقد أن هذا يستدعي الاحتفال.
Let's drink?
دعنا نشرب؟
Um, sissy Gemma, you seem a little quiet.
أوه، أختي جيما، تبدين هادئة بعض الشيء.
What's wrong? Um…
ما الخطب؟ اممم...
Is your body tired?
هل جسدك متعب؟
Or did your heart get tired after hearing
أم تعب قلبك بعد سماعه؟
that Mia and Patrick might be together?
أن ميا وباتريك قد يكونان معًا؟
You said it yourself, right?
لقد قلت ذلك بنفسك، أليس كذلك؟
We're not meant for each other.
نحن لسنا مناسبين لبعضنا البعض.
It's a waste to love someone who won't love you back.
إن حب شخص لا يحبك هو مضيعة للوقت.
I'm not saying I still have hope.
أنا لا أقول أني لا أزال أملك الأمل.
But it's still hard to accept.
ولكن لا يزال من الصعب قبول ذلك.
For me, this is what I believe in.
بالنسبة لي، هذا ما أؤمن به.
While you're still alive, there's always hope.
طالما أنك لا تزال على قيد الحياة، هناك دائمًا أمل.
But I hope I don't lose hope when it comes to being with you.
لكن أتمنى أن لا أفقد الأمل عندما يتعلق الأمر بالتواجد معك.
There's no use. Madeth's in the bathroom.
لا فائدة. ماديث في الحمام.
- Hurry, come over here. - Miss Li, hey!
- اسرعي، تعالي إلى هنا. - آنسة لي، هي!
Don't bother them. They might be talking about something important.
لا تُزعجهم، فقد يكونون يتحدثون عن أمرٍ مهم.
Mama Li, that's not fair.
ماما لي، هذا ليس عادلاً.
- Biases are for K-Pop fans. - Shh!
- التحيزات مخصصة لمحبي الكيبوب. - ششش!
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تحاول أن تقول؟
How come Vincent gets to flirt with Gemma and I don't?
كيف يمكن لفينسنت أن يغازل جيما وأنا لا؟
Okay, okay. I understand.
حسنًا، حسنًا. لقد فهمت.
I'm all for whoever my daughter wants, right?
أنا مع من تريده ابنتي، أليس كذلك؟
But for now, maybe sit this one out?
ولكن في الوقت الحالي، ربما عليك الجلوس خارج هذا الأمر؟
Alright? Come on.
حسناً؟ هيا.
Let's go get some fresh air. You look like you need it.
هيا بنا نستنشق بعض الهواء النقي. يبدو أنك بحاجة إليه.
Come on, come on.
هيا، هيا.
I'll even come with you.
سوف آتي معك أيضًا.
Has anyone ever told you how annoying you are?
هل أخبرك أحد من قبل بمدى إزعاجك؟
Of course. Many times.
بالطبع. مرات عديدة.
But I don't really see it as a bad thing.
لكنني لا أرى ذلك كأمر سيء حقًا.
I see it as part of my many endearing qualities.
أرى ذلك كجزء من العديد من الصفات المحببة لدي.
That's why you work for Mia.
لهذا السبب تعمل لدى ميا.
Hey! No.
مهلا! لا.
I'm the one who can handle Mia's annoying side.
أنا الشخص الذي يمكنه التعامل مع الجانب المزعج لميا.
Not the other way around.
وليس العكس.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
I'm still here in Maravida.
أنا لا أزال هنا في مارافيدا.
I didn't leave her alone.
لم أتركها وحدها.
And why is that?
ولماذا ذلك؟
You can go out and look for a different writer.
يمكنك الخروج والبحث عن كاتب مختلف.
But you keep following Mia like a lost puppy.
لكنك تستمر في متابعة ميا مثل جرو ضائع.
I don't know. I just can't leave her.
لا أعلم، لا أستطيع تركها.
You know, the thing about Mia.
هل تعلمين الشيء عن ميا؟
She won't admit it, but she's a very sad person.
إنها لن تعترف بذلك، لكنها شخص حزين جدًا.
Yes.
نعم.
Just like Patrick, I guess.
تمامًا مثل باتريك، على ما أعتقد.
He's good at hiding his feelings.
إنه جيد في إخفاء مشاعره.
He's good at avoiding his problems.
إنه جيد في تجنب مشاكله.
He's good at keeping secrets.
إنه جيد في حفظ الأسرار.
Maybe that's why he's a good match for Mia.
ربما لهذا السبب فهو مناسب لميا.
One more.
واحدة اخرى.
I don't want to drink anymore.
لا أريد أن أشرب بعد الآن.
- I've had enough. - Oh, come on.
- لقد حصلت على ما يكفي. - أوه، هيا.
Last drink.
الشراب الأخير.
- Last drink. - Oh, please.
- الشراب الأخير. - أوه، من فضلك.
Straight.
مستقيم.
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
I'm just so happy with the people I have in my life right now.
أنا سعيد جدًا بالأشخاص الموجودين في حياتي الآن.
Mm-hmm.
مممم.
I have a bestie who I like to call Matmat.
لدي صديقة مفضلة أحب أن أطلق عليها اسم ماتمات.
And…
و…
I have you.
انا أملكك.
Hmm.
همم.
Oh, you're blushing.
أوه، أنت تحمر خجلاً.
- No, I'm not. - Yes, you are.
- لا، لست كذلك. - نعم، أنت كذلك.
Hey.
يا.
You've fallen for me already, huh?
لقد وقعت في حبي بالفعل، أليس كذلك؟
No, Mia.
لا، ميا.
- Just admit it, Patrick. - No.
- فقط اعترف بذلك، باتريك. - لا.
I'm going to bed now, Mia.
سأذهب إلى السرير الآن، ميا.
Oh.
أوه.
Hmm?
همم؟
I told you you're drunk.
لقد قلت لك أنك سكران.
But not drunk in love with me.
ولكن ليس سكرانًا في حبي.
Go get some rest.
اذهب للحصول على بعض الراحة.
- Mia. - Hmm?
- لي. - همم؟
Go sleep at Kai's room.
اذهب للنوم في غرفة كاي.
Huh?
هاه؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Or stay with Bella. Wherever you want.
أو ابق مع بيلا، أينما تريد.
Patrick.
باتريك.
Oh, Patrick.
أوه، باتريك.
- Tomorrow… - Hmm?
- غداً... - همم؟
…Kai will go back to the hospital.
…كاي سوف يعود إلى المستشفى.
That means it's the lover's last night together.
وهذا يعني أن هذه هي الليلة الأخيرة للحبيبين معًا.
You should let them have this night for themselves.
ينبغي عليك أن تسمح لهم بالاستمتاع بهذه الليلة لأنفسهم.
Hey.
يا.
Don't you turn your back on me.
لا تدير ظهرك لي.
I want to see your face.
أريد أن أرى وجهك.
You smile more now.
أنت تبتسم أكثر الآن.
Like earlier on the beach.
كما في وقت سابق على الشاطئ.
And right now.
والآن.
I'm just happy I'm with you.
أنا سعيد جدًا بوجودي معك.
You make me smile.
أنت تجعلني ابتسم.
I can't stop it.
لا أستطيع إيقافه.
This isn't enough.
هذا ليس كافيا.
What?
ماذا؟
This isn't enough for me.
هذا ليس كافيا بالنسبة لي.
Hmm?
همم؟
Mia?
لي؟
Mia! Mia?!
لي! لي؟!
Mia, what are you going to do?
ميا ماذا ستفعلين؟
Mia! Mia!
لي! لي!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
- Mia, stop it. - Patrick.
- ميا، توقفي. - باتريك.
Stop playing hard to get.
توقف عن اللعب بالصعب الحصول عليه.
Mia, cut it out.
ميا، اقطعيها.
Patrick.
باتريك.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Who loves more?
من يحب أكثر؟
The moon, or the stars?
القمر أم النجوم؟
Hmm.
همم.
Who do you think…
من تعتقد…
has been there longer?
هل كان هناك لفترة أطول؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
I think,
أظن،
whoever's been up there longer,
من كان هناك لفترة أطول،
is more patient.
أصبح أكثر صبراً.
And whoever is more patient,
ومن كان أكثر صبراً
that's who loves more.
هذا هو من يحب أكثر.
Hmm.
همم.
You think so?
هل تعتقد ذلك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
That's how love is.
هكذا هو الحب.
If we'd gotten closer back then,
لو كنا أقرب في ذلك الوقت،
I wonder how things would be now.
أتساءل كيف ستكون الأمور الآن.
Mama would still be alive.
ماما سوف تظل على قيد الحياة.
Do you blame me?
هل تلومني؟
Do you know where they are?
هل تعرف أين هم؟
Something might happen to them.
ربما يحدث لهم شيء ما.
Don't leave Matmat, Patpat.
لا تترك ماتمات، باتبات.
Patpat's still not here.
باتبات ليس هنا بعد.
It's not because I'm enjoying my time or because I feel relaxed.
ليس لأنني أستمتع بوقتي أو لأنني أشعر بالاسترخاء.
but because you told me to not burden myself with regret.
لكن لأنك قلت لي ألا أثقل نفسي بالندم.
- They're beautiful. - Beautiful, just like you.
-إنهم جميلون. - جميلون، مثلك تمامًا.